Guide to the News Service subject files, 1930-ongoing
Duke University. University Archives
- Container List
  - Presidential Search Committee (Box 48)
  - Press Institute, 1941 (Box 48)
  - Press Institute, 1948-1949 (Box 48)
  - Press Institute, 1950 (Box 48)
  - Press Institute, 1951 (Box 48)
  - Press Institute, 1952 (Box 48)
  - Press Institute, 1953 (Box 48)
  - Press Institute, 1954 (Box 48)
  - Press Institute, 1955-1958 (Box 49)
  - Press Institute, 1959-1962 (2 folders) (Box 49)
  - Press Institute, 1963-1965 (2 folders) (Box 49)
  - Press Institute, 1966 (2 folders) (Box 49)
  - Press Institute, 1967-1968 (Box 49)
  - Press Institute, 1968-1969 (Box 49)
  - Press Institute, 1969 (Box 49)
  - Press Institute, 1970 (Box 49)
  - Press Photographers Short Course, 1960 (Box 49)
  - Primate Center (Box 49)
  - Professorships, James B. Duke (Box 50)
  - Project Opportunity (Box 50)
  - Progress Review (2 folders) (Box 50)
  - Prospective Students (Box 50)
  - Prospective Students, 1949-1961 (Box 50)
  - Prospective Students, 1962-1973 (Box 50)
  - Psychology, 1939-1965 (2 folders) (Box 50)
  - Psychology, 1966-1975 (Box 50)
  - Public Interest Research Group (Box 50)
  - Public Relations Meeting (Box 50)
  - Public School Administration (Box 50)
  - Publications Faculty (Box 50)
  - Quail Roost Conference Center, 1967 (Box 50)
  - Radio WDBS (Box 50)
  - R.E.L.C.V. Regional Education Laborator of the Carolinas and Virginia (Box 50)
  - Religion, 1953-1974 (Box 50)
  - Religion 1975-1976 (Box 51)
  - Religious Advisors (Box 51)
  - Religious Council (Box 51)
  - Religious Emphasis Week (Box 51)
  - Renaissance Meeting Southeastern (Box 51)
  - Research Grants (Box 51)
  - Research Triangle, 1958-1961 (Box 51)
  - Research Triangle, 1959-1961 (Box 51)
  - Research Triangle, 1961-1963 (2 folders) (Box 51)
  - Research Triangle, 1961-1964 (Box 51)
  - Research Triangle, 1965 (Box 51)
  - Research Triangle, 1966-1968 (2 folders) (Box 51)
  - Research Triangle, 1969-1970 (Box 52)
  - Research Triangle, 1971-1973 (Box 52)
  - Retired Employees (Box 52)
  - Retired Officers Training Program, 1958-1967 (Box 52)
  - Rice Diet (2 folders) (Box 52)
  - Romance Languages, 1949-1975 (Box 52)
  - ROTC, 1966-1978 (Box 52)
  - Rules of Law Center, 1958-1965 (2 folders) (Box 52)
  - Rules of Law Center, 1966-1970 (Box 52)
  - Russian Affairs Professorship (Box 52)
  - Sailing Club (Box 53)
  - Salute to Industry, 1958 (Box 53)
  - Sarah P. Duke Gardens, 1934-1960 (2 folders) (Box 53)
  - Sarah P. Duke Gardens, 1960-1966 (Box 53)
  - Sarah P. Duke Gardens, 1966-1974 (Box 53)
  - Scholarships (3 folders) (Box 53)
  - Scholarships, 1964-1967 (Box 53)
  - Scholarships, 1968-1978 (Box 53)
  - Scholarships A.B. Duke (Box 53)
  - Scholarship Marshall I. Pickens, 1969 (Box 53)
  - Scholarship W.N. Reynolds (Box 54)
  - School Law Conference (Box 54)
  - Science, General, 1964-1973 (Box 54)
  - Science Fairs, State, High School (Box 54)
  - Sciences and Humanities, 1974 (Box 54)
  - Science Mathematics Conference (Box 54)
  - Science Teachers Lab Conference, 1951-1952 (Box 54)
  - Securities Regulation Conference, 1964 November (Box 54)
  - Seminars, 1962-1970 (Box 54)
  - Sewage School, 1950 (Box 54)
  - Sewage School, 1953 (Box 54)
  - Shock and Vibrations Symposium College of Engineering (Box 54)
  - Sigma Xi (Box 54)
  - Slavic Languages, 1959-1975 (Box 54)
  - Social Studies Conference (Box 54)
  - Social System Simulation Program Economics and Mathematics, 1970 April (Box 54)
  - Societies and Organizations (2 folders) (Box 54)
  - Society of University Surgeons, 1951 February 8-11 (Box 54)
  - Sociology, 1940-1970 (Box 54)
  - Sociology, 1970-1976 (Box 54)
  - Sonny Burke Music Scholarship, 1962 (Box 54)
  - Sororities (Box 54)
  - South Atlantic Quarterly (Box 54)
  - Southeastern Renaissance Conference also S.E. Institute of Medieval and Renaissance Study (Box 54)
  - Southern Regional Educational Board (Box 54)
  - Southern Regional Growth Board (Box 55)
  - Space Symposium (2 folders) (Box 55)
  - Spanish Studies, 1936-1948 (Box 55)
  - Spanish Studies, 1949-1951 (Box 55)
  - Spanish Studies, 1952-1955 (Box 55)
  - Spanish, 1942-1967 (Box 55)
  - Spastic Clinic (Box 55)
  - Speaker Ban Law (4 folders) (Box 55)
  - Special Series Crisis on Our Coast and related articles (Box 55)
  - Sports Miscellaneous, 1944-1966 (Box 55)
  - Sports Scholarships (Box 55)
  - String Quartet at Duke including Ciompi (Box 55)
  - Students' Accomplishments, 1976-1986 (Box 55)
  - Student Activity, 1938-1948 (Box 55)
  - Student Activity, 1948-1950 (2 folders) (Box 56)
  - Student Activity, 1950-1953 (2 folders) (Box 56)
  - Student Activity, 1954-1955 (2 folders) (Box 56)
  - Student Activity, 1956-1957 (Box 56)
  - Student Activity, 1960 (Box 56)
  - Student Activity, 1961-1962 (Box 56)
  - Student Activity, 1963-1964 (Box 57)
  - Student Activity, 1965-1967 (Box 57)
  - Student Activity, 1968-1969 Racial Demonstrations, Sit-ins, etc. (Box 57)
  - Student Activity, 1968-1970 (Box 57)
  - Student Activity, 1970-1974 (Box 57)
  - Student Forum (Box 57)
  - Student Fundraising, 1976 (Box 57)
  - Students Foreign (Box 57)
  - Students General (2 folders) (Box 57)
  - Students General, 1974-1976 (Box 57)
  - Students General, 1977 (Box 58)
  - Students General, 1978 (Box 58)
  - Students General, 1979 (Box 58)
  - Students General, 1980 (Box 58)
  - Students General, 1981 (Box 58)
  - Students General, 1982 (Box 58)
  - Students General, 1983 (Box 58)
  - Student Government Workshop (Box 58)
  - Student Investment Trust (Box 58)
  - Student Legislature (Box 58)
  - Student Political Activities Participation in Political Campaigns (Box 58)
  - Student Political Activities Demonstrations, 1969-1971 (Box 58)
  - Student Political Activities Demonstrations, Allen Building Sit-In, 1969 (Box 58)
  - Student Political Activities Allen Building Sit-In, 1969 February (Box 58)
  - Student Political Activities Allen Building Sit-In, Editorials (Box 58)
  - Student Political Activities Demonstrations, 1970 (Box 59)
  - Student Political Activities, 1975-1976 (Box 59)
  - Student Union, 1960 (Box 59)
  - Student Union, 1961-1962 (Box 59)
  - Student Union, 1963-1965 (Box 59)
  - Student Union (5 folders) (Box 59)
  - Study Abroad (Box 59)
  - Summer Arts (Box 60)
  - Summer Concerts, 1948-1951 (Box 60)
  - Summer Science and Mathematics Institute (Box 60)
  - Summer Session, 1948-1949 (Box 60)
  - Summer Session, 1950-1952 (Box 60)
  - Summer Session, 1953-1955 (Box 60)
  - Summer Session, 1956-1965 (Box 60)
  - Summer Session, 1968-1976 (Box 60)
  - Summer Theater, 1975 (Box 60)
  - "Superior Student" Conference Gifted Children (Box 60)
  - Surtsey (Box 60)
  - Swimming (Box 60)
  - Symphony (Box 60)
  - Symposia (Box 60)
  - Symposium South and Sociology, 1962 July (Box 60)
  - Symposium on Women, 1963 (Box 60)
  - Tax Institute, 1949-1951 (Box 61)
  - Theology of Hope Symposium, 1968 April 4-6 (Box 61)
  - Tobacco Chemist's Research Conference, 1951 October (Box 61)
  - Tobacco Growing Research (Box 61)
  - Track Meets various (Box 61)
  - Track Meet/USA/USSR, 1974 (Box 61)
  - Triangle Symphony Orchestra (Box 61)
  - "Troika" (Box 61)
  - Tuition, 1975 (Box 61)
  - TUNL Triangle Universities Nuclear Laboratory (Box 61)
  - TV Day, August 1970 (Box 61)
  - United Fund (Box 61)
  - United Nations International Relations, 1969-1970 (Box 61)
  - United States Cadet Nurses Corps (Box 61)
  - University Center, 1976 (Box 61)
  - University of North Carolina (Box 61)
  - Urban Renewal, 1963 (Box 61)
  - V-12 Navy and Marines (Box 61)
  - Vietnam War Moratorium, etc. (Box 61)
  - Visiting Committees Law, Divinity, etc. (Box 61)
  - Visiting Professors (Box 61)
  - Visitors, 1941-1943 (Box 61)
  - Visitors, 1944-1952 (Box 61)
  - Lectures and Speakers, 1977-1980 (Box 64)
  - Lectures and Speakers, 1981 (Box 64)
  - Lectures and Speakers, 1982 (Box 64)
  - Lectures and Speakers, 1983 (Box 64)
  - Lectures and Speakers, 1984 (Box 64)
  - Lectures and Speakers, 1985 (Box 64)
  - Lectures and Speakers, 1986 (Box 64)
  - Lectures and Speakers, Fritz London Memorial Lecture, 1987 (Box 64)
  - Lectures and Speakers, 1988 (Box 64)
  - Lectures and Speakers, 1989 (Box 64)
  - Lecture Series, 1989-1990 (Box 64)
  - Lectures and Speakers, 1990 (Box 64)
  - Lectures and Speakers, 1991 (Box 64)
  - Lecture Series, 1991 (Box 64)
  - Lectures and Speakers, 1992 (Box 64)
  - Lecture Series, 1992 (Box 64)
  - Lectures and Speakers, 1993-1994 (Box 64)
  - Lectures and Speakers, 1994-1995 (Box 64)
  - Lectures and Speakers, 1996 (Box 64)
  - Legal Action Against Duke, 1983 (Box 64)
  - Legal Action Against Duke, 1987 (Box 64)
  - Legal Action Against Duke, 1988 (Box 64)
  - Legal Action, 1989 (Box 64)
  - Legal Action, 1990 (Box 64)
  - Legal Action, 1991 (Box 64)
  - Legal Action, 1992 (Box 64)
  - Legal Action, 1993 (Box 64)
  - Legal Action Against Duke, 1994-1996 (Box 64)
  - Liberal Studies (Box 64)
  - Lilly Scholars, 1975-1977 (Box 64)
  - Major Speakers, 1986 (Box 65)
  - Major Speakers, 1987 (Box 65)
  - Major Speakers, 1988 (Box 65)
  - Major Speakers, 1991 (Box 65)
  - Major Speakers, 1992-1995 (Box 65)
  - Major Speakers, 1996 (Box 65)
  - MAPS, back issues (Box 65)
  - Marine Lab, 1980 (Box 65)
  - Marine Lab, 1981 (Box 65)
  - Marine Lab, 1982-1983 (Box 65)
  - Marine Lab, 1983 (Box 65)
  - Marine Lab, 1984 (Box 65)
  - Marine Lab, 1985 (Box 65)
  - Marine Lab, 1986 (Box 65)
  - Marine Lab, 1987 (Box 65)
  - Marine Lab, 1988 (Box 65)
  - Marine Lab, 1989 (Box 65)
  - Marine Lab, 1990 (Box 65)
  - Martin Luther King Commemoration/Celebration, 1987 (Box 65)
  - Martin Luther King Commemoration/Celebration, 1988 (Box 65)
  - Martin Luther King Commemoration/Celebration, 1989 (Box 65)
  - Martin Luther King Commemoration/Celebration, 1991 (Box 65)
  - Mary Lou Williams Jazz Festival and Center for Black Culture (Box 65)
  - Mary Lou Williams Center and Jazz Festival, 1987 (Box 65)
  - Mary Lou Williams Center and Jazz Festival, 1988 (Box 65)
  - Mary Lou Williams Center and Jazz Festival, 1989 (Box 65)
  - Master of Arts of Liberal Studies (Box 65)
  - Mathematics Department of, 1966 (Box 65)
  - Mathematics Department of, 1988-1990 (Box 65)
  - Medical Alumnus Award, 1969 (Box 65)
  - Medical Alumni Association, 1972 (Box 65)
  - Medical Alumni Association, 1988 (Box 65)
  - Medical Center general, 1987 (Box 65)
  - Medical Center general, 1988 (Box 65)
  - Medical Center general, 1989 (Box 66)
  - Medical Center general, 1990 (Box 66)
  - Medical Center general, 1991 (Box 66)
  - Medical Center general, 1992 (2 folders) (Box 66)
  - Medical Center general, 1993 (2 folders) (Box 66)
  - Medical Center general, 1994 (2 folders) (Box 66)
  - Medical Center general, 1995 (2 folders) (Box 66)
  - Medical Center general, 1996 (Box 66)
  - Medical Center general, 1997 (2 folders) (Box 66)
  - Medicine Department of, 1989-1990 (Box 66)
  - Medicine Department of, 1992-1995 (Box 66)
  - Medical Engineering, 1988-1990 (Box 66)
  - Medical School, 1987 (Box 66)
  - Medieval and Renaissance Studies, 1982 (Box 66)
  - Medieval and Renaissance Studies, 1987 (Box 66)
  - Medieval and Renaissance Studies, 1988 (Box 66)
  - Messiah (Box 66)
  - Messiah, 1987 (Box 66)
  - Messiah, 1988 (Box 66)
  - Messiah, 1989-1990 (Box 66)
  - Microelectronics, 1987 (Box 66)
  - Microelectronics, 1988 (Box 66)
  - Microelectronics, 1989 (Box 66)
  - Microelectronics, 1981 (Box 67)
  - Minorities, 1988 (Box 67)
  - Minority Affairs, 1989 (Box 67)
  - Minority Affairs, 1990 (Box 67)
  - Minority Affairs, 1991 (Box 67)
  - Minority Affairs, 1992 (Box 67)
  - Minority Affairs, 1993 (Box 67)
  - Minority Affairs, 1994 (Box 67)
  - Minority Affairs, Racial Issues, Relations, 1995 (Box 67)
  - Minority Affairs, Racial Issues, Relations, 1997 (Box 67)
  - Music Building, Mary Duke Building, Dedicated October 1974 (Box 67)
  - Music Department (Box 67)
  - Music Department, 1975 (Box 67)
  - Music Department, 1977 (Box 67)
  - Music Department, 1978-1980 (Box 67)
  - Music Department, 1981 (Box 67)
  - Music Department, 1982 (Box 67)
  - Music Department, 1983 (Box 67)
  - Music Department, 1984 (Box 67)
  - Music Department, 1986 (Box 67)
  - Music Department, 1987 (Box 67)
  - Music Department, 1988 (Box 67)
  - Music Department, 1989 (Box 67)
  - Music Department, 1991 (Box 67)
  - Music Department, 1992 (Box 67)
  - Music Department, 1993 (Box 67)
  - Music Department, 1996 (Box 67)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1978 (Box 67)
  - National Humanities Center (Box 67)
  - National Humanities Center, Press Kit (Box 67)
  - National Humanities Center, 1975 (Box 67)
  - National Humanities Center, 1987 (Box 67)
  - National Humanities Center, 1988 (Box 67)
  - Living History Program, 1987 (Box 67)
  - National Merit Scholarship Foundation (Box 68)
  - National Science Foundation Cooperative Research Center (Box 68)
  - Naval ROTC, 1971 (Box 68)
  - NC Symphony (Box 68)
  - NC Symphony, 1977-1978 (Box 68)
  - Nobel Prize (Box 68)
  - Nobel Prize, 1989-1990 (Box 68)
  - NTE National Teacher Exams, 1973 (Box 68)
  - Nursing School of, 1975 (Box 68)
  - Nursing School of, 1988-1990 (Box 68)
  - Oak Ridge-Clinton Laboratories, 1975 (Box 68)
  - Office of Information Services (Box 68)
  - Olympics, 1987 (2 folders) (Box 68)
  - OPERA (Box 68)
  - Organization for Tropical Studies, 1985 (Box 68)
  - Panel Discussions (Box 68)
  - PCB Spill, 1979-1980 (Box 68)
  - Perkins Library Archives, 1989 (Box 68)
  - Perkins Library Archives, 1993 (Box 68)
  - Perkins Library, 1985 (Box 68)
  - Perkins Library, 1987 (Box 68)
  - Perkins Library, 1988 (Box 68)
  - Perkins Library, 1989 (Box 68)
  - Perkins Library, 1990 (Box 68)
  - Perkins Library, 1991 (Box 68)
  - Perkins Library, 1992 (Box 68)
  - Perkins Library System, 1993 (Box 68)
  - Perkins Library System, 1994 (Box 68)
  - Perkins Library System, 1995 (Box 68)
  - Perkins Library System, 1996 (Box 68)
  - Perkins Library System, 1997 (Box 68)
  - News Service. Subject Files, 1930-1998 (Box 69)
  - Library, 1975-1984 (2 folders) (Box 69)
  - Library, 1977-1984 (Box 69)
  - Personnel Non-Academic, 1977-1986 (Box 69)
  - Personal Rapid Transit (Box 69)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1975 (Box 69)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1988 (Box 69)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1989-1990 (Box 69)
  - Philosophy, 1970 (Box 69)
  - Philosophy, 1988-1990 (Box 69)
  - Physics (Box 69)
  - Physics, 1975 (Box 69)
  - Physics, 1983 (Box 69)
  - Physics, 1985 (Box 69)
  - Physics, 1989 (Box 69)
  - Physics, 1990 (Box 69)
  - Physics, 1991 (Box 69)
  - Physical Planning Department, 1980 (Box 69)
  - Phytotron, 1975 (Box 69)
  - Phytotron, 1987 (Box 69)
  - Phytotron, 1988 (Box 69)
  - Phytotron, 1989 (Box 69)
  - Phytotron, 1990 (Box 69)
  - PIRG NC Public Interest Research Group (Box 69)
  - Pitchforks, 1985 (Box 69)
  - Placement Center, 1975 (Box 69)
  - Placement Office, 1987 (Box 69)
  - Placement Office, 1988 (Box 69)
  - Placement Office, 1989 (Box 69)
  - Policies and Regulations (Box 69)
  - Policies and Regulations, 1987 (Box 69)
  - Policies and Regulations, 1988 (Box 69)
  - Policies and Regulations, 1991 (Box 69)
  - Press Institute, 1975 (Box 69)
  - Policies and Regulations, 1990 (Box 70)
  - Political Activities (Box 70)
  - Political Science, 1982 (Box 70)
  - Political Science, 1983 (Box 70)
  - Political Science, 1985 (Box 70)
  - Political Science, 1986 (Box 70)
  - Political Science, 1987 (Box 70)
  - Political Science, 1988 (Box 70)
  - Political Science, 1989-1990 (Box 70)
  - Political Science, 1991 (Box 70)
  - Political Science, 1993 (Box 70)
  - Political Science, 1994 (Box 70)
  - Political Science, 1996 (Box 70)
  - Pollution and Environment, 1982 (Box 70)
  - Post Office (Box 70)
  - Presidents Duke (Box 70)
  - President's Report to Trustees, 1984 (Box 70)
  - Press Association, NC, 1975 (Box 70)
  - Press Briefing, Nov. 1972, Coastal Environment (Box 70)
  - Press Briefing, Feb. 18, 1974, Secondary/Elementary Education (Box 70)
  - Press Briefings (Box 70)
  - Press Institute, 1975 (Box 70)
  - Primate Center, 1975-1984 (2 folders) (Box 70)
  - Primate Center, 1985 (Box 70)
  - Primate Center, 1987 (Box 70)
  - Primate Center, 1988 (Box 70)
  - Primate Center, 1989 (Box 70)
  - Primate Center 1990 (Box 70)
  - Primate Center, 1991 (Box 70)
  - Primate Center, 1992 (Box 70)
  - Primate Center, 1993 (Box 70)
  - Primate Center, 1994 (Box 70)
  - Primate Center, 1996 (Box 70)
  - Professorships, James B. Duke, Henry Luce (Box 70)
  - Public Safety (Box 71)
  - Public Safety, 1987 (Box 71)
  - Public Safety, 1988 (Box 71)
  - Public Safety, 1991 (Box 71)
  - Public Safety, 1992 (Box 71)
  - Public Safety, 1993 (Box 71)
  - Public Safety and Crime, 1993 (Box 71)
  - Public Safety and Crime, 1996 (Box 71)
  - Public Safety and Crime, 1997 (Box 71)
  - Public Safety and Crime, 1998 (Box 71)
  - Publications, 1986 (Box 71)
  - Publications, 1987 (Box 71)
  - Publications, 1988 (Box 71)
  - Publications, 1989 (Box 71)
  - Publications, 1990 (Box 71)
  - Publications, 1991 (Box 71)
  - Prospective Students, 1988 (Box 71)
  - Psychology, 1976-1984 (Box 71)
  - Psychology, 1982 (Box 71)
  - Psychology, 1983 (Box 71)
  - Psychology, 1985 (Box 71)
  - Psychology, 1986 (Box 71)
  - Psychology, 1987 (Box 71)
  - Psychology, 1988 (Box 71)
  - Psychology, 1989-1990 (Box 71)
  - Psychology, 1991 (Box 71)
  - Rankings, 1985 (Box 71)
  - Rankings, 1987 (Box 71)
  - Rankings, 1988 (Box 71)
  - Rankings, 1989 (Box 71)
  - Rankings, 1990 (Box 71)
  - Rankings, 1991 (Box 71)
  - Rankings, 1992-1993 (Box 71)
  - Rankings, 1994 (Box 71)
  - Rankings, 1995 (Box 71)
  - Rankings, 1996 (Box 71)
  - Radio Station- WDBS (Box 71)
  - Radio Station- WXD4 (Box 71)
  - Radio Station- WXD4, 1988 (Box 71)
  - Religion, 1975-1984 (Box 71)
  - Religion, 1985 (Box 71)
  - Religion, 1986 (Box 71)
  - Religious Activities-Students, 1987 (Box 71)
  - Religion, 1988 (Box 71)
  - Religious Activities- Students, 1988 (Box 71)
  - Religious Activities-Students, 1989-1990 (Box 71)
  - Religion, 1989-1990 (Box 71)
  - Religion, 1991 (Box 71)
  - Religious Activities, 1991 (Box 71)
  - READ, 1986 (Box 72)
  - Research Grants (Box 72)
  - Research Studies, 1980 (2 folders) (Box 72)
  - Research Studies Medical, 1987 (Box 72)
  - Research Studies Medical, 1988 (Box 72)
  - Research Studies Medical, 1989 (Box 72)
  - Research Studies Medical, 1990 (Box 72)
  - Research Studies Medical, 1991 (Box 72)
  - Research Studies Medical, 1992 (Box 72)
  - Research Studies Medical, 1993 (Box 72)
  - Research Studies Medical, 1994 (Box 72)
  - Research Studies Medical, 1995 (Box 72)
  - Research Studies University, 1987 (Box 72)
  - Research Studies University, 1988 (Box 72)
  - Research Studies University, 1989 (Box 72)
  - Research Studies University, 1990 (Box 72)
  - Research Studies University, 1991 (Box 72)
  - Research Studies University, 1992 (Box 72)
  - Research Studies University, 1993 (Box 72)
  - Research Triangle, 1974-1984 (2 folders) (Box 72)
  - Research Triangle, 1985 (Box 72)
  - Research Triangle Institute, 1987 (Box 72)
  - Research Triangle Institute, 1988 (Box 72)
  - Research Triangle Institute, 1989 (Box 72)
  - Resource and Environmental Policy Research Center (Box 72)
  - Retired Employees (Box 72)
  - Retrenchment, 1980 (Box 72)
  - Rice Diet, 1976-1978 (Box 73)
  - Rice Diet, 1977 (Box 73)
  - Rice Diet, 1980 (Box 73)
  - Rice Diet, 1987 (Box 73)
  - Rice Diet, 1988 (Box 73)
  - Rice Diet, 1989-1990 (Box 73)
  - Rice Diet, 1991 (Box 73)
  - Romance Languages (Box 73)
  - Romance Languages and Literature, 1988-1990 (Box 73)
  - ROTC, 1975-1985 (Box 73)
  - ROTC, 1987 (Box 73)
  - ROTC, 1988 (Box 73)
  - ROTC, 1989-1990 (Box 73)
  - ROTC, 1991 (Box 73)
  - AFROTC (Box 73)
  - Roundtable on Science and Public Affairs (Box 73)
  - Roundtable on Science and Public Affairs, 1987 (Box 73)
  - Roundtable on Science and Public Affairs, 1988 (Box 73)
  - Run for Your Life (Box 73)
  - Savoyards (Box 73)
  - Scholarships, 1975 (2 folders) (Box 73)
  - Scholarships General, 1987 (Box 73)
  - Scholarships General, 1988 (Box 73)
  - Scholarships General, 1989 (Box 73)
  - Scholarships General, 1990 (Box 73)
  - Scholarships General, 1991 (Box 73)
  - Scholarships General, 1992 (Box 73)
  - Scholarships General, 1995-1996 (Box 73)
  - A.B. Duke Scholarship, 1971-1976 (Box 73)
  - A.B. Duke Scholarship, 1987 (Box 73)
  - A.B. Duke Scholarship, 1988 (Box 73)
  - Scholarship Medical, B. Everett Jordan (Box 73)
  - B.N. Duke Scholarship (Box 73)
  - B.N. Duke Scholarship, 1987 (Box 73)
  - B.N. Duke Scholarship, 1989 (Box 73)
  - Braxton Craven Scholarship (Box 73)
  - Braxton Craven Scholarship, 1973 (Box 73)
  - North Carolina Scholars, 1987 (Box 73)
  - Mark D. MacFarlane Scholarship (Box 73)
  - Posey Scholarship (Box 73)
  - Reginald Howard Scholarship, 1977 (Box 73)
  - Rhodes Scholars, 1987 (Box 73)
  - Rhodes Scholars, 1989-1990 (Box 73)
  - Sarah W. and Marshall I. Pickens Scholarship (Box 73)
  - Sigmund Sternberger Scholarship (Box 73)
  - School of the Environment, 1996 (Box 73)
  - School of the Environment, 1997 (Box 73)
  - South Atlantic Quarterly, 1977-1978 (Box 73)
  - Science general, 1980-1985 (Box 74)
  - Science general, 1990 (Box 74)
  - Science general, 1991 (Box 74)
  - Science Resource Initiative, 1988 (Box 74)
  - Science Resource Initiative, 1991 (Box 74)
  - Science, Technology and Human Values, 1988-1990 (Box 74)
  - Search Committee (Box 74)
  - Sesquicentennial Celebration (Box 74)
  - Sesquicentennial Celebration, 1989-1990 (Box 74)
  - Shroud of Turin (2 folders) (Box 74)
  - Slavic Languages and Literature, 1959- (Box 74)
  - Slavic Languages and Literature, 1988-1990 (Box 74)
  - Sociology, 1978-1981 (Box 74)
  - Sociology, 1982 (Box 74)
  - Sociology, 1983 (Box 74)
  - Sociology, 1985 (Box 74)
  - Sociology, 1986 (Box 74)
  - Sociology, 1988 (Box 74)
  - Sociology, 1989-1990 (Box 74)
  - Sociology, 1991- (Box 74)
  - Sororities (Box 74)
  - South-East Consortium, 1980 (Box 74)
  - Sports Festival, 1984- (Box 74)
  - String Quartet, 1987 (2 folders) (Box 74)
  - String Quartet, 1988 (Box 74)
  - String Quartet, 1988-1990 (Box 74)
  - String Quartet, 1991 (Box 74)
  - Student Accomplishments, 1977 (Box 74)
  - Student Accomplishments, 1978 (Box 74)
  - Student Accomplishments, 1979 (Box 74)
  - Student Accomplishments, 1980 (Box 74)
  - Student Accomplishments, 1981 (Box 74)
  - Student Accomplishments, 1982 (Box 74)
  - Student Accomplishments, 1983 (Box 74)
  - Student Accomplishments, 1984 (Box 74)
  - Student Accomplishments, 1986 (Box 74)
  - Student Accomplishments, 1987 (Box 74)
  - Student Accomplishments, 1988 (Box 74)
  - Student Accomplishments, 1989 (Box 74)
  - Student Accomplishments, 1990 (Box 74)
  - Student Accomplishments, 1991 (Box 74)
  - Student Awards and Honors, 1975 (Box 74)
  - Student Awards and Honors, 1987 (Box 74)
  - Student Awards and Honors, 1988 (Box 74)
  - Student Awards and Honors, 1989 (Box 74)
  - Student Awards and Honors, 1991 (Box 74)
  - Student Organizations, 1989 (Box 74)
  - Student Organizations, 1991 (Box 74)
  - Students, Political, 1987 (Box 74)
  - Students, Political, 1988 (Box 74)
  - Students, Political, 1989 (Box 74)
  - Students, Political, 1991 (Box 74)
  - ASDU Associated Students of Duke University, 1991 (Box 75)
  - Students, Clubs, 1975 (Box 75)
  - Students, Clubs, 1987 (Box 75)
  - Students, Clubs, 1988 (Box 75)
  - Students, Committees, 1987. (Box 75)
  - Students, Committees, 1988 (Box 75)
  - Students, Committees, 1989 (Box 75)
  - Students, Committees, 1990 (Box 75)
  - Students, Deaths, 1975 (Box 75)
  - Students, Deaths, 1989 (Box 75)
  - Students, Deaths, 1991-1993 (Box 75)
  - Students, General, 1984 (Box 75)
  - Students, General, 1985 (2 folders) (Box 75)
  - Students, General, 1986 (Box 75)
  - Students, General, 1987 (2 folders) (Box 75)